Actually, I believe there's so many
things women can do better than guys.
Women can do things like here's one
example that I I was at the mall with my
nephew babysitting. I'm just walking
through the mall and a woman I didn't
know pulled up a knee. She goes, "Is
that your son?" I go, "No, it's my
nephew." And she she without any
hesitation, she says, "He is adorable.
What's your name? You are so cute.
Marcus, when you turn 18, I'm coming
back for you. You're a little
heartbreaker. Save him for me." He
walked away. Went back to shopping. I
challenge any man in this room.
Any guy, go to the mall. Just approach a
woman you don't know. Is that your
niece? Can I have a word with her,
please?
Wow. When you turn 18, I'm coming back
for you.
Save her for me. That's a good one.
You don't get to walk out of the mall.
They escort you out of the
was just talking to kids. That's right,
R. Kelly. Tell it to the judge. Tell it
to the
[Applause]
>> There's things women can do. How about
it's Valentine's Day or maybe your girl
misses you and she sends you a romantic
picture. You're like, "Whoa, you're
excited. Maybe it's been a long day at
work. Oo, can't wait to get home. She
misses me." Women can send those
romantic pictures. But men, if you send
a picture of you laying in the beach,
rolling around in the sand,
bending over in a speedo, when you
coming home, babe,
you're not going to get a positive
reaction.
A lot of guys are getting busted for
taking those romantic pictures. Here's
what I do. I turn this show into a TED
talk. I teach men how to take the best,
most seductive picture for the women in
this room. Here's what you do, guys. Go
home, get in the closet, and put all
your clothes on. Your best clothes.
Don't take anything off. Put on your
dress shoes, dress socks, dress pants,
belt, shirt, tie, suit, coat, briefcase.
Make it look like you're going to work.
If you really want to turn her on, let
your 401k dangle out of the front of the
briefcase. Just
a little tip. And just a little tip
because I did I did the most amazing
show recently. I was on a yacht on
Mother's Day for 150 mothers in Orange
County, California. Newport Beach on a
yacht going around the harbor and it was
beautiful and the women were beautiful
and I was the only man on the cruise.
Picture that. 150 Orange County moms and
me. And it felt good. They laughed at my
jokes and I knew if the yacht were to
sink, those women would float.
Have you been to Orange County?
If they had been on the Titanic, Jack
would have survived.
Orange County women, they come with
their own flotation devices. They just
be waiting for help to arrive. Just
waiting
waiting. Some of Not all of them. Not
some of them float different. Just
But that's still sea level. They're
okay. They're okay.
The only ones I was worried about are
the younger ones. They flow different.
They're
[Applause]
sun's out, buns out.
Those mothers were beautiful. And one of
the moms, I go, "How old are you?" She
goes, "I won't tell you my age, but I'm
about 25 years older than you are." I
go, "My, you look younger than me." She
goes, "Well, I have a spa. you should
come to my day spa and I'm going to do a
treatment for you. Now, I would never do
something like this, but she said my
favorite word, free.
So, go I go in there and she goes,
"We're going to do cryogenic face
freezing for you." And I never even
heard that. She goes, "Here's what it
is." She basically blew a blow dryer on
my face full of dry ice. One minute. She
goes, "That would have been 60 bucks.
What did you think?" I said, "That would
have been a ripoff." She goes, "What do
you mean? That's a really good
treatment." I was like, "No, cuz I'm
older now. I'm smart. I know you get the
same experience at Costco in the produce
section.
You know what I'm talking about. Where's
my bulk members? That's what's up. Go in
there in the summer, do your whole body
for $65.
You get a sample on the way out. You're
good.
Yeah. That's what I like. You get wisdom
when you get older. So, I don't mind.
Like the other day, I invited a girl
over to Netflix and chill and that's all
we did. It was awesome.
The one thing I don't like about getting
older is the fashion keeps moving
forward. Every generation wants to have
their own fashion. And now the skinny
jeans are the thing. And look at these
pants.
Some of you mocked them when I came out.
Look at those pants. I didn't design
these. I bought them. This is what they
offer. I'm from the '9s. We wore cargo
pants back then. Any men still wear
cargo pants? Any real men? Yeah. See,
real men wear Where's the men wearing
skinny jeans? Where you at? Yeah. And
the rest wanted to clap, but they're too
tight. It's like I can't even
It's painful. Real men wear cargo pants.
If you called a plumber and he showed up
in skinny jeans, would you trust that
man?
It looks yucky to me, too.
[Applause]
Not one of these
cargo pants, man. Get in there. I'll fix
this for you. You'll be back at this
toilet in no time.
That's what you need. A fireman, a
police officer, the military, cargo
pants. That was me in the ' 90s. I had
so many pockets. I didn't even know what
to do with all the pockets. One time I
moved from one apartment to the other
just with my pants. I didn't even need
to U-Haul budget truck. Uh got my futon,
my big screen TV, potted plants.
Everything was in those pants, man. I
miss those. And you got to understand
like I was like a young guy. I was like
puka shell necklace wearing dude.
with a button-down shirt going to the
club but baggy I was boyband up top
gangster rapper down below
and I felt good cuz at the club you
could dance with cargo pants and even if
you didn't know how to dance the pants
covered up all that footwork you didn't
have to know
girls like you're good it's like no you
just can't see what's going on under
here this is horrible
I feel like Ellen DeGeneres what is it
with these pants you got to know what
you're doing on the dance floor. Plus,
when you put them on as a man, you don't
feel very good. When women put on tight
pants, you feel fierce. Ready to take
over the club. Yeah, that's right. She's
wearing them.
Feel fierce. When men put on skinny
jeans, we're making decisions the whole
way up. All right. What's going down the
left? What's going down the right? It's
going to be there for
you guys. A little while. I expected
that.
You got to make decisions. And then you
look in the mirror and you feel feminine
immediately. When you wear skinny jeans,
you can't help it. That's why it's
called H&M. Put them on, you're like,
hm.
These are the pants. You're saying, why
are you wearing them? Cuz I perform for
college kids, then comedy clubs and
cruise ships. So, I do the whole thing.
But for the kids, you want to look like
them. But I don't like these pants. When
you go to the club back in the day, you
had your cargo pants. Listen up,
children. We used to wear cargo pants to
the club. And you were a better man. Cuz
a girl be like, "Babe, I'm dancing. It's
so much fun. I want you to hold my lip
gloss." You're like, "Give me that. I
got a pocket for that right there."
You could hold her lip gloss. Baby, give
me your keychains. I got that right over
here. Pow. I got moisturizer. I got
Visine. I had a pharmacy in my pants.
Everything was in there. Girl, you look
thirsty. Take a water. You can keep that
one. I got I got a whole 24 pack. Okay,
I'm good.
just dance all night. You are an
extension of her purse.
I think it's a conspiracy theory to take
men's power away. Cuz now that we're
wearing skinny jeans, we're not valuable
anymore. We go to the club, ladies.
You're like, "Babe, hold my lip gloss."
You're like, "I don't got no room for
that."
You want equal rights. This is what it
looks like. You're
[Applause]
You fought for this. Remember,
[Music]